Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory6 Mss.B.B61.inventory06
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents H
  - Hilbers, Henry (Box 40)
    - To Boas, 1935 Jan. 22; 1p.
  - Hildreth, E.L. & Co. (Box 40)
    - From Boas, 1919 Sept. 15; 2p.
  - Hildreth, Gertrude H. (Box 40)
    - From Boas, 1937 Dec. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Dec. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Apr. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 May 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 May 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 June 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 June 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Nov. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Nov. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Dec. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 May 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 June 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Oct. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 May 24; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Oct. 20; 1p.
    - (Enc: Tests), 1939 Nov. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Nov. 7; 1p.
  - Hilfe gegen Hitler (Box 40)
    - To Boas, 1937 end; 4p.
  - Hilka, Alfons (Box 40)
    - To Boas, 1922 Sept. 21; 2p.
  - Hill, A.H. (Box 40)
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 24; 4p.
  - Hill, G.W.C. (Box 40)
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 10; 5p.
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 9; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 6; 3p.
  - Hill, H.W. (Box 40)
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 20; 1p.
  - Hill, James J. (Box 40)
    - From Boas, 1904 Jan. 25; 1p.
  - Hill, John W. (Box 40)
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 16; 1p.
  - Hill, P.A. (Box 40)
    - From Boas, 1928 Feb. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Feb. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Feb. 25; 1p.
  - Hill, Ralph C. (Box 40)
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 21; 1p.
  - Hill, Walter C. (Box 40)
    - To Boas, 1894? Mar. 20
  - Hiller, E.T. (Box 40)
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 25; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Apr. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 22; 1p.
  - Hillquit, M. (Box 40)
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 10; 1p.
  - Hills, E.C. (Box 40)
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Oct. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 May 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Aug. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Sept.7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 30; 1p.
  - Hillyer, Mary W. (Box 40)
    - From Boas, 1936 Oct. 20; 1p.
    - (Enc: Note on socialism.), 1942 Apr. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Sept. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Feb. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 May 6; 1p.
  - Hilprecht, Herman V. (Box 40)
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 25; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 28; 4p.
  - Hilts, H.M. (Box 40)
    - To Boas, 1934 July 2; 1p.
  - Himes, Norman E. (Box 40)
    - From Boas, 1930 Sept. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Sept. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Sept. 11; 1p.
  - Himmelheber, H. (Box 40)
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 3; 1p.
  - Himstead, R.E. (Box 40)
    - From Boas, 1938 Dec. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Dec. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 20; 1p.
  - Hinckley, William W. (Box 40)
    - From Boas, 1936 Nov. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Nov. 17; 2p.
    - (Enc: Roosevelt, F.D. to Hinckley, W.W. Papers re American Youth Congress), 1939 Feb. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Feb. 15; 1p.
    - W.W. Hinckley -- from F.D. Roosevelt
      - (Enc. with Hinckley, W.W., Nov. 17, 1936)
  - von Hindenburg, Paul, Field Marshal (Box 40)
    - From Boas, 1933 Mar. 27; 3p.
    - P. von Hindenburg -- from G. Fasting, 1924 Aug. 15
  - Hinds, C.H. (Box 40)
    - To Boas, 1934 June 29; 1p.
  - Hinneberg, Paul (Box 40)
    - From Boas, 1907 Sept. 12
    - From Boas, 1933 June 7; 1p.
  - Hinsdale, Ellen C. (Box 40)
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 1; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 28; 2p.
  - Hippel, A. v. (Box 40)
    - To Boas
    - (Enc. with Breit, G. to Dunn, L.C., Feb. 17, 1935)
  - Hirsch, Alfred H. (Box 40)
    - From Boas, 1933 Oct. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Jan. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 May 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Oct. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Aug. 13; 1p.
    - (Enc: National committee for the defense of political prisoners. Minutes of Aug. 2, 1934), 1934 Nov. 20; 1p.
    - (Attached: 2 clippings), 1937 Oct. 18; 1p.
    - A.H. Hirsch -- from H.M. Kallen, 1934 Dec. 18
    - (Enc. with Kallen, H.M. Dec. 18, 1934), 1934 Dec. 26
    - To Boas, 1934 Dec. 26
    - (Enc. with Hirsch, A.H. to Kallen, H.M., Jan. 9, 1935)
    - A.H. Hirsch -- to H. M. Kallen, 1935 Jan. 9; 2p.
  - Hirsch, Caesar (Box 40)
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 13; 2p.
  - Hirsch, H.R. (Box 40)
    - From Boas, 1934 Sept.7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Sept.8; 1p.
  - Hirsch, I. Seth (Box 40)
    - From Boas, 1930 Jan. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Mar. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Mar. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Apr. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Jan. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Mar. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Mar. 11; 1p.
  - Hirsch, Max (Box 40)
    - To Boas, 1885 June 25
    - To Boas, 1885 June 26
  - Hirsch, N.D.M. (Box 40)
    - From Boas, 1926 Nov. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Aug. 25; 2p.
  - Hirschmann, Ira A. (Box 40)
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 June 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Feb. 4; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1940 May 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Oct. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Apr. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 May 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Dec. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Dec. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 Jan. 7; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1942 Jan. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Mar. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Oct. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 May 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Dec. 31; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Jan. 9; 2p.
  - Hirt, Arnold (Box 40)
    - To Boas, 1890 June 23; 2p.
    - To Boas, n.d.; 3p.
  - Hirt, Ferdinand & Sohn (Box 40)
    - To Boas, 1890 June 23; 2p.
    - To Boas, n.d.; 3p.
  - Hirth, Friedrich (Box 40)
    - From Boas, 1904 Nov. 14; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Nov. 14; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1905 Apr. 13
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 7
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 6
    - To Boas, 1904 Mar. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Dec. 6
    - F. Hirth -- from B. Laufer, 1905 Jan. 20
  - Hirtzel, W. Harry (Box 40)
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Mar. 29; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 26; 1p.
  - Hirtzel, Y.T.H. (Box 40)
    - From Boas, 1919 Nov. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 31; 1p.
  - Historical Department of Iowa (Box 40)
    - To American Ethnological Society, 1908 Oct. 9
  - Hitchcock, C.N. (Box 40)
    - From Boas, 1928 July 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 July 23; 1p.
    - (Enc: Hitchcock, C.N., Aug. 3, 1927.)
  - Hitchcock, Henry S. (Box 40)
    - To Boas, 1911 May 10
    - To Boas, 1911 May 27
  - Hitchcock, L.S. (Box 40)
    - From Boas, 1927 Feb. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Jan. 17; 1p.
  - Hitt, R.R. (Box 40)
    - To Boas, 1902 Dec. 16; 1p.
  - Hittij, J. (Box 40)
    - J. Hittij -- to Dr. A. Jacob, 1884 Oct. 11
  - Hitze von (Box 40)
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 27
  - Hobart, Harold C. (Box 40)
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 3; 1p.
  - Hobbs, R.P. (Box 40)
    - To Boas, 1939 July 11; 1p.
  - Hobbs, William H. (Box 40)
    - From Boas, 1916 Mar. 6
    - From Boas, 1936 May 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 May 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 May 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Apr. 6; 1p.
  - Hocart, A.M. (Box 40)
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 19; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1919 May 2; 2p.
  - Hochschild, B. (Box 40)
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 26; 1p.
  - Hock, L. (Box 40)
    - To Boas, 1898 July 15; 2p.
  - Hocker (Box 40)
    - To Boas, 1933 May 25; 10p.
  - Hockett, Charles (Box 40)
    - From Boas, 1940 May 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Dec.; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Mar. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 June 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 July 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Oct. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 May 6; 1p.
  - Hodge, C.F. (Box 40)
    - To Boas, 1899 Mar. 5; 2p.
  - Hodge, Frederick Webb (Box 40-41)
    - From Boas, 1898 Nov. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1898 Nov. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1898 Nov. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1898 Dec. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1898 Dec. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1898 Dec. 13
    - From Boas, 1898 Dec. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1899 Jan. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1899 Jan. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1899 Jan. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1899 Jan. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1899 Jan. 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1899 Feb. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1899 Feb. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1899 Mar. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1899 Mar. 3; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1899 Mar. 11; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1899 Mar. 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1899 Apr. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1899 Apr. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1899 May 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1899 June 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1899 June 12
    - From Boas, 1899 Aug. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1899 Sept. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1899 Nov. 15
    - From Boas, 1899 Dec. 18; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1899 Dec. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1900 Jan. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1900 Mar. 2; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1900 Mar. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1900 Mar. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1900 Mar. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1900 Mar. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1900 Apr. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1900 Apr. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1900 Apr. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas (2), 1990 May 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1990 May 3
    - From Boas, 1990 May 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1990 Sept. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1990 Oct. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1990 Oct. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1990 Oct. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1990 Oct. 11; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1990 Oct. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1990 Oct. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1990 Nov. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1990 Nov. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1990 Dec. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1990 Dec. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1901 Jan. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1901 Jan. 26
    - From Boas, 1901 Jan. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1901 Feb. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1901 Feb. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1901 Feb. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1901 Feb. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1901 Mar. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1901 Mar. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1901 Apr. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1901 May 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1901 May 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1901 May 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1902 Mar. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1902 Mar. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1902 Mar. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1902 Mar. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1902 Apr. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1902 Apr. 9
    - From Boas, 1902 Apr. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1902 Apr. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1902 May 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1902 June 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Oct. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Dec. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Dec. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904
      (N.D.C.Hodges)
    - From Boas, 1904 Dec. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Apr. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Oct. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Nov. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Nov. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1905 Mar. 14
    - From Boas, 1905 May 27
    - From Boas, 1905 June 1
    - From Boas, 1905 June 3
    - From Boas, 1905 June 5
    - From Boas, 1905 June 12
    - From Boas, 1905 July 14
    - From Boas, 1905 Oct. 4
    - From Boas, 1905 Oct. 13
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 1
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 8
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 20
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 17
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 15
    - From Boas, 1906 Apr. 6
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 14
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 19
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 15
    - From Boas, 1907 May 2
    - From Boas, 1907 May 21
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 12
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 17
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 22
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 31
    - From Boas, 1907 Sept. 11
    - From Boas, 1908 Mar. 16
    - From Boas, 1908 Mar. 19
    - From Boas, 1908 Mar. 25
    - From Boas, 1908 Apr. 27
    - From Boas, 1908 May 4
    - From Boas, 1908 June 9; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1908 June 11
    - From Boas, 1908 June 13
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 3
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 27; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 30; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1908 Dec. 18
    - From Boas, 1908 Dec. 22
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 10
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 16
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 18; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 20
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 1
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 7
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 7
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 16
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 29; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1909 May 12
    - From Boas, 1909 May 19
    - From Boas, 1909 May 27
    - From Boas, 1909 June 11
    - From Boas, 1909 June 14
    - From Boas, 1909 June 30
    - From Boas, 1910 Feb. 7; 6p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Feb. 15
    - From Boas, 1910 Feb. 15; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Feb. 19; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Feb. 26; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 14; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1910 May 12
    - From Boas, 1910 May 20
    - From Boas, 1910 May 28
    - From Boas, 1910 May 28
    - From Boas, 1910 June 15
    - From Boas, 1910 Aug. 11; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Nov. 14; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1911 Feb. 1
    - From Boas, 1911 Mar. 9; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1911 Mar. 31; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1911 Apr. 6; 4p.
    - From Boas, 1911 Apr. 15
    - From Boas, 1911 May 1
    - From Boas, 1911 May 9; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1911 May 10
    - From Boas, 1911 May 11
    - From Boas, 1911 May 23
    - From Boas, 1911 May 27
    - From Boas, 1911 May 29; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1911 June 5
    - From Boas, 1911 June 8; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1911 June 10
    - From Boas, 1911 June 13
    - From Boas, 1911 June 22; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1911 June 22; 6p.
    - From Boas, 1911 Nov. 8
    - From Boas, 1912 Aug. 10; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 3; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 20
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 2
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 3
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 4; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 6
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 13; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 15
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 22
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 23; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 29
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 31
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 31
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 3; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 4
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 10
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 11
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 14
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 18
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 18
    - From Boas, 1913 Mar. 10; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1913 July 8
    - From Boas, 1913 July 9
    - From Boas, 1913 July 9
    - From Boas, 1913 July 9; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1913 July 18
    - From Boas, 1913 July 19; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1913 July 23
    - From Boas, 1913 July 23
    - From Boas, 1913 July 24
    - From Boas, 1913 Aug. 7
    - From Boas, 1913 Aug. 10
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 20
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 20
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 28
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 16
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 17
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 18
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 20; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 2
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 2
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 2; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 4
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 9
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 11 and 23
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 26
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 27
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 2; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 3; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 5
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 5
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 7
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 8; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 12; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 15; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 22; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 24
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 29; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 4; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 5
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 11; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 12; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 17
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 17
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 21; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1914 Mar. 16
    - From Boas, 1914 Mar 20; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1914 Mar. 30
    - From Boas, 1914 May 23
    - From Boas, 1914 July 1; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1914 Nov. 10
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 2; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 5
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 7
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 8; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 9
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 12; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 14
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 16
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 16
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 20
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 25
    - From Boas, 1915 Feb. 8; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1915 Feb. 13
    - From Boas, 1915 Feb. 18
    - From Boas, 1915 Feb. 18
    - From Boas, 1915 Feb. 24
    - From Boas, 1915 Feb. 27
    - From Boas, 1915 Mar. 9
    - From Boas, 1915 Mar. 23; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1915 Apr. 13; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1915 Apr. 13; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1915 Apr. 15
    - From Boas, 1915 May 21
    - From Boas, 1915 May 27; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1915 May 28
    - From Boas, 1915 Aug. 3; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1915 Nov. 24; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1916 Feb. 28
    - From Boas, 1916 Mar. 17; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1916 May 22
    - (See Boas, F. to Gordon, G.B. May 22, 1916), 1916 May 25; 4p.
    - From Boas, 1916 Sept. 27; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1916 Sept. 29
    - From Boas, 1916 Oct. 18
    - From Boas, 1916 Oct. 21
    - From Boas, 1916 Nov. 20; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1916 Dec. 8
    - (See Boas, F. to Dixon, R.B. Dec. 8, 1916), 1917 Oct. 31
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 19; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 15; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Nov. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Dec. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 June 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Mar. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1894 July 23
    - To Boas, 1894 Sept. 16
    - To Boas, 1896 Jan. 7
    - To Boas, 1898 Apr. 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Oct. 26; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Oct. 29; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Oct. 31; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Nov. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Nov. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Nov. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Nov. 26; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Dec. 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Dec. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Dec. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Dec. 9; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Dec. 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Dec. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Dec. 28; 2p.
    - (list, Foreign members, Anthrop. Soc. Washington), 1898 Dec. 30; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1898 see end
    - To Boas, 1899 Jan. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Jan. 3; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Jan. 8; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Jan. 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Jan. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Jan. 14; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Jan. 23; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Jan. 25; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Jan. 26; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Feb. 1; postcard
    - To Boas, 1899 Feb. 3; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Feb. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Feb. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Feb. 7; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Feb. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Feb. 17; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Mar. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Mar. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Mar. 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Mar. 6
    - To Boas, 1899 Mar. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Mar. 13; 7p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Mar. 14; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Mar. 15; 7p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Mar. 16; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Mar. 18; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Mar. 22; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Mar. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Mar. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas (2), 1899 Apr. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Apr. 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Apr. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Apr. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Apr. 27 and Apr. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 May 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 May 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 May 4; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1899 May 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 May 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1899 May 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 May 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 May 29; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1899 May 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 June 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1899 June 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 June 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 June 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 June 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 July 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Sept.; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Sept. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Sept. 12; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Sept. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Sept. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Oct. 13; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Oct. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Nov. 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Nov. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Nov. 30; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Dec. 5; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Dec. 6; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Dec. 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Dec. 8; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Dec. 14; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Dec. 19; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Dec. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Dec. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1900 Jan. 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1900 Jan. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1900 Jan. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1900 Feb. 1
    - To Boas, 1900 Feb. 6; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1900 Mar. 1; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1900 Mar. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1900 Mar. 10; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1900 Mar. 21; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1900 Apr. 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1900 Apr. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1900 Apr. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1900 Apr. 27; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1900 Apr. 27; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1900 Apr. 30
    - To Boas, 1900 May 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1900 May 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1900 May 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1900 May 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1900 May 25; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1900 Sept. 26; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1900 Oct. 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1900 Oct. 12; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1900 Oct. 12; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1900 Nov. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1900 Nov. 20
    - To Boas, 1900 Dec. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1901 Jan. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1901 Jan. 31; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1901 Feb. 16; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1901 Feb. 27; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1901 Mar. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1901 May 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1901 May 27; 2p.
    - To Boas, n.d.; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1902 Mar. 4; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1902 Mar. 31
    - To Boas, 1902 Apr. 8; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1902 Apr. 14
    - To Boas, 1902 May 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1902 June 3
    - To Boas, 1902 June 16
    - To Boas, 1902 Aug. 16
    - To Boas, 1902 Aug. 26; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1902 Sept.4
    - To Boas, 1902 Sept. 12
    - To Boas, 1903 Feb. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Mar. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Apr. 19; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Apr. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Aug. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Sept. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Sept. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Oct. 14; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Oct. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Oct. 19; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Nov. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Dec. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Dec. 21; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Mar. 19; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Mar. 6
    - To Boas, 1905 May 19
    - To Boas, 1905 May 22
    - To Boas, 1905 May 26
    - To Boas, 1905 June 9
    - To Boas, 1905 July 7
    - To Boas, 1905 July 20
    - To Boas, 1905 July 21
    - To Boas, 1905 Aug. 28
    - To Boas, 1905 Sept. 6
    - To Boas, 1905 Sept. 20
    - To Boas, 1905 Oct. 4
    - To Boas, 1905 Oct. 18
    - To Boas, 1905 Oct. 24
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 11
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 20
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 6
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 15
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 28
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 10
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 18; (card)
    - To Boas, 1906 June 2
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 15
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 26
    - To Boas, 1907 Feb. 18
    - To Boas, 1907 Feb. 25
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 19
    - To Boas, 1907 May 24
    - To Boas, 1907 Aug. 14
    - To Boas, 1907 Aug. 17
    - To Boas, 1907 Sept. 3
    - To Boas, 1907 Sept. 13
    - See Kroeber, A.L. to Hodge, F.W. Oct. 29, 1907, 1907 Dec. 9
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 21; postcard
    - To Boas, 1908 Feb. 26
    - To Boas, 1908 Mar. 17
    - To Boas, 1908 Mar. 19
    - To Boas, 1908 Mar. 21
    - To Boas, 1908 Mar. 26
    - To Boas, 1908 Apr. 30
    - To Boas, 1908 June 12
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 2
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 6
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 28
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 28; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 31
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 16
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 3
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 4
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 5
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 7; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 8
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 16
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 16
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 21
    - To Boas, 1909 Jan. 7; postcard
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 5
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 9
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 16